BU Records: Office of the President (Abner Vernon McCall), Inclusive: 1845-1981, undated, Bulk: 1961-1981
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- People, 1927-1981, undated; 4
  - Mosi-Mr Correspondence, 1959-1981 (Box 209, Folder 2)
  - Muc-Murd Correspondence, 1959-1981 (Box 209, Folder 3)
  - Murp-Murr Correspondence, 1959-1980 (Box 209, Folder 4)
  - Mus-My Correspondence, 1959-1977 (Box 209, Folder 5)
  - Malone, Orba Lee, 1958-1978 (Box 209, Folder 6)
  - Martin, D. K., 1952-1960 (Box 209, Folder 7)
  - Martin, D. K., 1961 (Box 209, Folder 8)
  - Martin, D. K. (1 of 2), 1962 (Box 210, Folder 1)
  - Martin, D. K. (2 of 2), 1962 (Box 210, Folder 2)
  - Martin, D. K., 1963 (Box 210, Folder 3)
  - Martin, D. K., 1964 (Box 210, Folder 4)
  - Martin, D. K., 1965-1978 (Box 210, Folder 5)
  - Mathis, [Marie] Mrs. R. L., 1959-1968 (Box 210, Folder 6)
  - Mathis, [Marie] Mrs. R. L., 1970-1978 (Box 210, Folder 7)
  - McKay, Connally, 1959-1978 (Box 210, Folder 8)
  - McKellar, J. M., 1962 (Box 210, Folder 9)
  - McKnight, Roy J., 1958-1968 (Box 211, Folder 1)
  - McLean, Marrs and Verna, 1947-1969 (Box 211, Folder 2)
  - McMurrey Estate, 1962-1966 (Box 211, Folder 3)
  - Middleton, C. E., 1942-1968 (Box 211, Folder 4)
  - Morriss, L. L., 1960-1979 (Box 211, Folder 5)
  - Moyers, Bill, 1959-1979 (Box 211, Folder 6)
  - Naa-Nan Correspondence, 1959-1981 (Box 211, Folder 7)
  - Nas-Nee Correspondence, 1959-1980 (Box 212, Folder 1)
  - Nef-Newb Correspondence, 1959-1980 (Box 212, Folder 2)
  - Newc-Newm Correspondence, 1959-1978 (Box 212, Folder 3)
  - Newp-Nic Correspondence, 1959-1980 (Box 212, Folder 4)
  - Nie-Nob Correspondence, 1961-1980 (Box 212, Folder 5)
  - Nok-Norr Correspondence, 1960-1978 (Box 212, Folder 6)
  - Nors-Norw Correspondence, 1959-1980 (Box 212, Folder 7)
  - Not-Ny Correspondence, 1962-1978 (Box 212, Folder 8)
  - Nesbitt, Laura Dell, 1964-1965 (Box 212, Folder 9)
  - Newman, Guy D., 1959-1980 (Box 212, Folder 10)
  - Nixon, Richard, 1968-1974 (Box 212, Folder 11)
  - Oa-Og Correspondence, 1959-1981 (Box 213, Folder 1)
  - Oh-Ol Correspondence, 1959-1979 (Box 213, Folder 2)
  - On-Os Correspondence, 1959-1978 (Box 213, Folder 3)
  - Ot-Ox Correspondence, 1959-1978 (Box 213, Folder 4)
  - Olson, Stanley P., 1959-1961 (Box 213, Folder 5)
  - O’Malley, Charles J., 1964 (Box 213, Folder 6)
  - Pac-Parke Correspondence, 1959-1978 (Box 213, Folder 7)
  - Parks-Patr Correspondence, 1959-1979 (Box 213, Folder 8)
  - Patterson, B-Patterson, J, 1960-1980 (Box 213, Folder 9)
  - Patterson, P-Pau Correspondence, 1959-1981 (Box 214, Folder 1)
  - Pax-Pen Correspondence, 1959-1979 (Box 214, Folder 2)
  - Peo-Pete Correspondence, 1959-1981 (Box 214, Folder 3)
  - Petz-Phe Correspondence, 1959-1980 (Box 214, Folder 4)
  - Phi-Pie Correspondence, 1959-1980 (Box 214, Folder 5)
  - Pil-Pitt Correspondence, 1959-1980 (Box 214, Folder 6)
  - Pitz-Ply Correspondence, 1960-1980 (Box 214, Folder 7)
  - Pod-Pop Correspondence, 1960-1979 (Box 215, Folder 1)
  - Por-Powel Correspondence, 1959-1981 (Box 215, Folder 2)
  - Power-Presc Correspondence, 1960-1981 (Box 215, Folder 3)
  - Presl-Price Correspondence, 1959-1980 (Box 215, Folder 4)
  - Prich-Prou Correspondence, 1960-1981 (Box 215, Folder 5)
  - Prov Correspondence, 1960-1981 (Box 215, Folder 6)
  - Pru-Py Correspondence, 1959-1979 (Box 215, Folder 7)
  - Perry, W. C., 1959-1960 (Box 215, Folder 8)
  - Piazza, Tina, 1960 (Box 216, Folder 1)
  - Poage, W. R., 1959-1968 (Box 216, Folder 2)
  - Poage, W. R., 1969-1975 (Box 216, Folder 3)
  - Porter, Para, 1967-1970 (Box 216, Folder 4)
  - Powers, Louis T., 1962 (Box 216, Folder 5)
  - Presley, Dewey, 1959-1968 (Box 216, Folder 6)
  - Presley, Dewey, 1969-1975 (Box 216, Folder 7)
  - Q Correspondence, 1960-1977 (Box 216, Folder 8)
  - Rab-Ral Correspondence, 1959-1981 (Box 216, Folder 9)
  - Ram-Ran Correspondence, 1959-1979 (Box 216, Folder 10)
  - Rap-Raw Correspondence, 1959-1981 (Box 217, Folder 1)
  - Ray-Reag Correspondence, 1959-1980 (Box 217, Folder 2)
  - Ream-Redd Correspondence, 1959-1980 (Box 217, Folder 3)
  - Redf-Rei Correspondence, 1959-1979 (Box 217, Folder 4)
  - Rel-Rice Correspondence, 1961-1980 (Box 217, Folder 5)
  - Rick-Rid Correspondence, 1960-1981 (Box 217, Folder 6)
  - Rie-Ritc Correspondence, 1959-1979 (Box 217, Folder 7)
  - Ritt-Robers Correspondence, 1959-1975 (Box 217, Folder 8)
  - Robert-Roberts Correspondence, 1959-1979 (Box 218, Folder 1)
  - Robertson-Robi Correspondence, 1960-1981 (Box 218, Folder 2)
  - Roc-Roe Correspondence, 1959-1975 (Box 218, Folder 3)
  - Rog-Rogg Correspondence, 1959-1979 (Box 218, Folder 4)
  - Roh-Rouse, M Correspondence, 1960-1980 (Box 218, Folder 5)
  - Rouse, R Correspondence, 1959-1963 (Box 218, Folder 6)
  - Routh-Ruc Correspondence, 1959-1979 (Box 218, Folder 7)
  - Rudd-Russell, H Correspondence, 1959-1979 (Box 219, Folder 1)
  - Russell, J-Rust Correspondence, 1954-1977 (Box 219, Folder 2)
  - Rut-Ry Correspondence, 1960-1978 (Box 219, Folder 3)
  - Rayzor, J. Newton, 1960-1970 (Box 219, Folder 4)
  - Rieber, Morton, 1965-1966 (Box 219, Folder 5)
  - Royals, Mr. and Mrs. R. W., 1965-1968 (Box 219, Folder 6)
  - Russell, Willard L., 1959-1971 (Box 219, Folder 7)
  - Rouse, Ruth (Thelma), 1964 (Box 219, Folder 8)
  - Sab-Sam Correspondence, 1959-1980 (Box 219, Folder 9)
  - San-Sap Correspondence, 1959-1979 (Box 220, Folder 1)
  - Sar-Schn Correspondence, 1959-1980 (Box 220, Folder 2)
  - Scho-Schr Correspondence, 1959-1980 (Box 220, Folder 3)
  - Schu-Schw Correspondence, 1961-1979 (Box 220, Folder 4)
  - Sco-Scu Correspondence, 1961-1979 (Box 220, Folder 5)
  - Sea-Selm Correspondence, 1959-1979 (Box 220, Folder 6)
  - Selt-Shah Correspondence, 1962-1978 (Box 220, Folder 7)
  - Shan-Shee Correspondence, 1959-1979 (Box 221, Folder 1)
  - Shei-Sher Correspondence, 1959-1979 (Box 221, Folder 2)
  - Shi-Shu Correspondence, 1959-1978 (Box 221, Folder 3)
  - Sib-Sim Correspondence, 1960-1979 (Box 221, Folder 4)
  - Sin-Skin Correspondence, 1959-1981 (Box 221, Folder 5)
  - Skip-Smil Correspondence, 1959-1981 (Box 221, Folder 6)
  - Smith, A-Smith, C Correspondence, 1959-1977 (Box 221, Folder 7)
  - Smith, D-Smith G Correspondence, 1959-1978 (Box 222, Folder 1)
  - Smith, H-Smith, J Correspondence, 1959-1981 (Box 222, Folder 2)
  - Smith, K-Smith, P Correspondence, 1959-1979 (Box 222, Folder 3)
  - Smith,R-Smith W Correspondence, 1959-1981 (Box 222, Folder 4)
  - Smo-Sor Correspondence, 1959-1981 (Box 222, Folder 5)
  - Sou-Spa Correspondence, 1959-1980 (Box 222, Folder 6)
  - Spe-Spr Correspondence, 1960-1977 (Box 222, Folder 7)
  - Spu-Stan Correspondence, 1959-1978 (Box 223, Folder 1)
  - Stap-Sten Correspondence, 1959-1979 (Box 223, Folder 2)
  - Step-Ster Correspondence, 1959-1979 (Box 223, Folder 3)
  - Stev Correspondence, 1961-1980 (Box 223, Folder 4)
  - Stew-Stoh Correspondence, 1959-1980 (Box 223, Folder 5)
  - Stok-Stor Correspondence, 1959-1981 (Box 223, Folder 6)
  - Stou-Stra Correspondence, 1960-1979 (Box 223, Folder 7)
  - Stre-Stri Correspondence, 1960-1979 (Box 223, Folder 8)
  - Stro-Sur Correspondence, 1960-1978 (Box 224, Folder 1)
  - Sut-Suz Correspondence, 1960-1980 (Box 224, Folder 2)
  - Sw-Sz Correspondence, 1959-1978 (Box 224, Folder 3)
  - Sadler, M. E., 1959-1966 (Box 224, Folder 4)
  - Sandoz, Ellis, 1973-1979 (Box 224, Folder 5)
  - Shamburger, W. M., 1961-1979 (Box 224, Folder 6)
  - Shearin, George, 1959-1973 (Box 224, Folder 7)
  - Sherman, Cecil, 1961-1978 (Box 224, Folder 8)
  - Skipper, Mary, 1964-1978 (Box 224, Folder 9)
  - Smith, Preston, 1964-1978 (Box 224, Folder 10)
  - Smitherman, Nellie Norton, 1963 (Box 225, Folder 1)
  - Standley, W. G., 1965-1966 (Box 225, Folder 2)
  - Sublett, L. R., 1962-1965 (Box 225, Folder 3)
  - Summers, Ray, 1963-1975 (Box 225, Folder 4)
  - Tab-Tan Correspondence, 1959-1979 (Box 225, Folder 5)
  - Tap-Tau Correspondence, 1961-1980 (Box 225, Folder 6)
  - Tay Correspondence, 1959-1978 (Box 225, Folder 7)
  - Tea-Ter Correspondence, 1959-1980 (Box 225, Folder 8)
  - Tew-Thomp Correspondence, 1959-1980 (Box 225, Folder 9)
  - Thoms-Tir Correspondence, 1959-1980 (Box 225, Folder 10)
  - Tis-Tor Correspondence, 1959-1979 (Box 226, Folder 1)
  - Tot-Trim Correspondence, 1960-1980 (Box 226, Folder 2)
  - Trip-Tub Correspondence, 1961-1977 (Box 226, Folder 3)
  - Tuc-Turna Correspondence, 1959-1977 (Box 226, Folder 4)
  - Turne-Ty Correspondence, 1959-1979 (Box 226, Folder 5)
  - Teal, Gordon K., 1960-1975 (Box 226, Folder 6)
  - Teal, Gordon K., 1976-1978 (Box 226, Folder 7)
  - Tower, John G., 1962-1972 (Box 226, Folder 8)
  - Tower, John G., 1973-1975 (Box 227, Folder 1)
  - Tower, John G., 1976-1980 (Box 227, Folder 2)
  - Trantham, Henry, 1962-1967 (Box 227, Folder 3)
  - Turner, Thomas (Tommy) E., 1959-1969 (Box 227, Folder 4)
  - U Correspondence, 1959-1980 (Box 227, Folder 5)
  - Vad-Van Correspondence, 1959-1980 (Box 227, Folder 6)
  - Var-Vaz Correspondence, 1959-1975 (Box 227, Folder 7)
  - Ve-Vr Correspondence, 1959-1978 (Box 227, Folder 8)
  - Wac-Wah Correspondence, 1959-1981 (Box 228, Folder 1)
  - Wald-Walk Correspondence, 1959-1980 (Box 228, Folder 2)
  - Wall-Walt Correspondence, 1961-1981 (Box 228, Folder 3)
  - Wam-Warr Correspondence, 1959-1980 (Box 228, Folder 4)
  - Was-Watson, B Correspondence, 1959-1979 (Box 228, Folder 5)
  - Watson, C-Wea Correspondence, 1960-1980 (Box 228, Folder 6)
  - Web-Wei Correspondence, 1959-1978 (Box 228, Folder 7)
  - Welc-Well Correspondence, 1959-1979 (Box 229, Folder 1)
  - Wen-Wess Correspondence, 1960-1977 (Box 229, Folder 2)
  - West Correspondence, 1959-1980 (Box 229, Folder 3)
  - Wet-White, D Correspondence, 1959-1981 (Box 229, Folder 4)
  - White, F-White, T Correspondence, 1959-1981 (Box 229, Folder 5)
  - White, W-Whitt Correspondence, 1959-1981 (Box 229, Folder 6)
  - Wib-Wile Correspondence, 1959-1979 (Box 229, Folder 7)
  - Wilh-Wilk Correspondence, 1968-1978 (Box 229, Folder 8)
  - Willa-Williams, H Correspondence, 1959-1979 (Box 230, Folder 1)
  - Williams, J-Williams, N Correspondence, 1961-1981 (Box 230, Folder 2)
  - Williams, P — Willin Correspondence, 1959-1979 (Box 230, Folder 3)
  - Willis-Wills Correspondence, 1961-1979 (Box 230, Folder 4)
  - Wils-Wilt Correspondence, 1959-1979 (Box 230, Folder 5)
  - Wim-Win Correspondence, 1959-1979 (Box 230, Folder 6)
  - Wir-Wol Correspondence, 1959-1980 (Box 230, Folder 7)
  - Wom-Wooda Correspondence, 1959-1979 (Box 231, Folder 1)
  - Woodc-Wool Correspondence, 1959-1979 (Box 231, Folder 2)
  - Woot-Wra Correspondence, 1959-1979 (Box 231, Folder 3)
  - Wri-Wy Correspondence, 1959-1980 (Box 231, Folder 4)
  - Wathen, Mrs. M. M., 1964-1965 (Box 231, Folder 5)
  - Watson, Charles E., 1966-1975 (Box 231, Folder 6)
  - Watson, Murray, 1959-1965 (Box 231, Folder 7)
  - Watson, Murray, 1966-1969 (Box 231, Folder 8)
  - Watson, Murray, 1970-1978 (Box 231, Folder 9)
  - Westmoreland, Dr. E. H., 1963-1976 (Box 232, Folder 1)
  - White, W. R., 1948-1981 (Box 232, Folder 2)
  - Willers, Jack, 1960-1961 (Box 232, Folder 3)
  - Williams, Ben H., 1955-1958 (Box 232, Folder 4)
  - Williams, Ben H. (1 of 2), 1959-1960 (Box 232, Folder 5)
  - Williams, Ben H. (2 of 2), 1959-1960 (Box 232, Folder 6)
  - Williams, Ben H., 1961-1964 (Box 232, Folder 7)
  - Williams, Ben H., 1965-1966 (Box 232, Folder 8)
  - Williams, Ben H., 1967-1969 (Box 233, Folder 1)
  - Williams, Ben H., 1970 (Box 233, Folder 2)
  - Williams, Ben H., 1971 (Box 233, Folder 3)
  - Williams, Ben H., 1972-1977 (Box 233, Folder 4)
  - Wood, James E., 1960-1979 (Box 233, Folder 5)
  - Wooten, Ben H., 1959-1968 (Box 233, Folder 6)
  - Yah-Yar Correspondence, 1960-1976 (Box 233, Folder 7)
  - Yat Correspondence, 1927-1979 (Box 234, Folder 1)
  - Yea-Yor Correspondence, 1959-1980 (Box 234, Folder 2)
  - You-Yu Correspondence, 1959-1981 (Box 234, Folder 3)
  - Z Correspondence, 1960-1980 (Box 234, Folder 4)
- Personal, 1956-1981, undated; 5
  This series includes personal files kept with McCall's presidential materials as well as his appointment books, correspondence relating to engagements McCall was asked to attend, letters labeled by their tone (critical, "onion", or "orchid"), speeches, telegrams received and sent, and desk memorabilia such as plaques and trinkets. For a more detailed list of desk memorabilia, please contact the University Archivist. Letters labeled as "onion" letters were typically critical in tone while letters labeled as "orchid" were complimentary. This series is in average condition.
  - Abner McCall Personal File, 1960-1963 (Box 234, Folder 5)
  - Abner McCall Personal File, 1965-1970 (Box 234, Folder 6)
  - Appointment Books, 1959-1960 (Box 234, Folder 7)
  - Appointment Books, 1961-1962 (Box 235, Folder 1)
  - Appointment Books, 1963-1964 (Box 235, Folder 2)
  - Appointment Books, 1965-1966 (Box 235, Folder 3)
  - Appointment Books, 1967-1969 (Box 235, Folder 4)
  - Appointment Book, 1970 (Box 236, Folder 1)
  - Appointment Book, 1971 (Box 236, Folder 2)
  - Appointment Book, 1972 (Box 236, Folder 3)
  - Appointment Book, 1973 (Box 236, Folder 4)
  - Appointment Book, 1974 (Box 237, Folder 1)
  - Appointment Book, 1975 (Box 237, Folder 2)
  - Appointment Book, 1976 (Box 237, Folder 3)
  - Appointment Book, 1977 (Box 238, Folder 1)
  - Appointment Book, 1978 (Box 238, Folder 2)
  - Appointment Book, 1979 (Box 238, Folder 3)
  - Appointment Book, 1980 (Box 239, Folder 1)
  - Appointment Book, 1981 (Box 239, Folder 2)
  - Critical Letters, 1963-1964 (Box 239, Folder 3)
  - Engagements Accepted (1 of 2), 1960-1961 (Box 239, Folder 4)
  - Engagements Accepted (2 of 2), 1960-1961 (Box 239, Folder 5)
  - Engagements Accepted, 1963 (Box 239, Folder 6)
  - Engagements Accepted (1 of 2), 1964 (Box 240, Folder 1)
  - Engagements Accepted (2 of 2), 1964 (Box 240, Folder 2)
  - Engagements Accepted (1 of 2), 1965 (Box 240, Folder 3)
  - Engagements Accepted (2 of 2), 1965 (Box 240, Folder 4)
  - Engagements Accepted, 1966 (Box 240, Folder 5)
  - Engagements Accepted (1 of 3), 1967 (Box 240, Folder 6)
  - Engagements Accepted (2 of 3), 1967 (Box 240, Folder 7)
  - Engagements Accepted (3 of 3), 1967 (Box 240, Folder 8)
  - Engagements Accepted (1 of 3), 1968 (Box 241, Folder 1)
  - Engagements Accepted (2 of 3), 1968 (Box 241, Folder 2)
  - Engagements Accepted (3 of 3), 1968 (Box 241, Folder 3)
  - Engagements Accepted (1 of 3), 1969 (Box 241, Folder 4)
  - Engagements Accepted (2 of 3), 1969 (Box 241, Folder 5)
  - Engagements Accepted (3 of 3), 1969 (Box 241, Folder 6)
  - Engagements Accepted (1 of 3), 1970 (Box 241, Folder 7)
  - Engagements Accepted (2 of 3), 1970 (Box 242, Folder 1)
  - Engagements Accepted (3 of 3), 1970 (Box 242, Folder 2)
  - Engagements Accepted, 1971 (Box 242, Folder 3)
  - Engagements Accepted, 1972-1975 (Box 242, Folder 4)
  - Engagements Filled, 1959 (Box 242, Folder 5)
  - Engagements Filled, 1960 (Box 242, Folder 6)
  - Engagements Filled, 1961 (Box 242, Folder 7)
  - Engagements Filled (1 of 3), 1962 (Box 242, Folder 8)
  - Engagements Filled (2 of 3), 1962 (Box 243, Folder 1)
  - Engagements Filled (3 of 3), 1962 (Box 243, Folder 2)
  - Engagements Filled (1 of 3), 1963 (Box 243, Folder 3)
  - Engagements Filled (2 of 3), 1963 (Box 243, Folder 4)
  - Engagements Filled (3 of 3), 1963 (Box 243, Folder 5)
  - Engagements Filled (1 of 2), 1964 (Box 243, Folder 6)
  - Engagements Filled (2 of 2), 1964 (Box 243, Folder 7)
  - Engagements Filled (1 of 2), 1965 (Box 244, Folder 1)
  - Engagements Filled (2 of 2), 1965 (Box 244, Folder 2)
  - Engagements Filled (1 of 2), 1966 (Box 244, Folder 3)
  - Engagements Filled (2 of 2), 1966 (Box 244, Folder 4)
  - Engagements Not Accepted, 1959-1960 (Box 244, Folder 5)
  - Engagements Not Accepted, 1961 (Box 244, Folder 6)
  - Engagements Not Accepted (1 of 2), 1962 (Box 244, Folder 7)
  - Engagements Not Accepted (2 of 2), 1962 (Box 245, Folder 1)
  - Engagements Not Accepted (1 of 2), 1963 (Box 245, Folder 2)
  - Engagements Not Accepted (2 of 2), 1963 (Box 245, Folder 3)
  - Engagements Not Accepted (1 of 3), 1964 (Box 245, Folder 4)
  - Engagements Not Accepted (2 of 3), 1964 (Box 245, Folder 5)
  - Engagements Not Accepted (3 of 3), 1964 (Box 245, Folder 6)
  - Engagements Not Accepted (1 of 3), 1965 (Box 245, Folder 7)
  - Engagements Not Accepted (2 of 3), 1965 (Box 246, Folder 1)
  - Engagements Not Accepted (3 of 3), 1965 (Box 246, Folder 2)
  - Engagements Not Accepted (1 of 2), 1966 (Box 246, Folder 3)
  - Engagements Not Accepted (2 of 2), 1966 (Box 246, Folder 4)
  - Engagements Not Accepted (1 of 2), 1967 (Box 246, Folder 5)
  - Engagements Not Accepted (2 of 2), 1967 (Box 246, Folder 6)
  - Engagements Not Accepted (1 of 2), 1968 (Box 246, Folder 7)
  - Engagements Not Accepted (2 of 2), 1968 (Box 246, Folder 8)
  - Engagements Not Accepted, 1969 (Box 246, Folder 9)
  - Engagements Not Accepted, 1970 (Box 247, Folder 1)
  - Engagements Not Accepted, 1971 (Box 247, Folder 2)
  - Engagements Not Accepted, 1972-1973 (Box 247, Folder 3)
  - Engagements Not Accepted, 1974-1976 (Box 247, Folder 4)
  - Engagements Pending, 1962-1966 (Box 247, Folder 5)
  - “Onion Letters”, 1965-1968 (Box 247, Folder 6)
  - “Orchid Letters” (1 of 2), 1961-1968 (Box 247, Folder 7)
  - “Orchid Letters” (2 of 2), 1961-1968 (Box 248, Folder 1)
  - Speeches (1 of 2), 1956-1977, undated (Box 248, Folder 2)
  - Speeches (2 of 2), 1956-1977, undated (Box 248, Folder 3)
  - Speeches and Articles, 1961-1969 (Box 248, Folder 4)
  - Speeches and Articles, 1970-1980 (Box 248, Folder 5)
  - Speeches - Baptists, 1960-1966, undated (Box 248, Folder 6)
  - Speeches - Law, 1960, undated (Box 248, Folder 7)
  - Speeches - Patriotism, 1976 (Box 249, Folder 1)
  - Speeches (Reference Materials), 1957-1967, undated (Box 249, Folder 2)
  - Speeches - Texas Breakfast Club, 1977 (Box 249, Folder 3)
  - Telegrams - In, 1959-1962 (Box 249, Folder 4)
  - Telegrams - In, 1963-1966 (Box 249, Folder 5)
  - Telegrams - Out, 1959-1964 (Box 249, Folder 6)
  - Telegrams [In and Out], 1967-1969 (Box 249, Folder 7)
  - Desk Memorabilia (Box 250 OVZ)
  - Desk Memorabilia (Box 251 OVZ)